megamillions.com 2019-04-17

# Mega Millions

Mega Millions respects absolutely the privacy of every person visiting our website.

##### Personal Information and IP Addresses

Mega Millions will not collect any personal information about you (i.e., your name, address, telephone number, or email address) unless you provide it to us voluntarily. If you have access to the Internet, your computer automatically has an Internet Protocol ("IP") address. We use IP addresses to gather information to track the number of visitors to our website and to identify our most popular pages so we can improve site content.

The only ways we can obtain your personal information are if you submit it to us through one of our interactive forms or send us a general inquiry or feedback.

If you do not want your personal information collected, please do not submit it to us! If you have already sent this information to us and would like for us to delete it, please email us at [webmaster@megamillions.com](mailto:webmaster@megamillions.com "MegaMillions Inquiry")

##### Communicating With Us

While visiting our website, you may want to send Mega Millions an email or request that we call you. If so, we may ask you to provide your name, the subject of your question or comment, and your email address or telephone number. This information is used solely to fulfill your online request. Mega Millions does not seek to share this information with any other entity.

##### Information Collected and How It Is Used

If you do nothing during your visit to the Mega Millions website but browse or download information, we automatically collect and store the following information about your visit:

The Internet Domain and IP address from which you accessed our site. The type of browser and operating system you used. The date and time you visited our site. The pages visited. If you linked from another website, the address of that website. The information collected is used to improve the content of our web services and help us understand how people are using our pages. We analyze our website logs to continually improve the value of the materials available on our site. The information in our web logs is not personally viewable and no attempt is made to link it with individuals who browse our website.

If during your visit to the Mega Millions website you send an email message, we collect your email address and the contents of the message you sent us. We use your email address to respond to you.

##### Public Disclosure

Except as specified above, Mega Millions does not collect personal information.

Mega Millions does not seek to share, sell or trade email addresses, information collected in surveys or in our guest book, or any other information about our online visitors. However, Mega Millions will disclose user information if we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against an individual who attempts, even unintentionally, to gain unauthorized access to Mega Millions information or to disrupt our website.

##### Cookies

When you visit the Mega Millions website and request information, this site's server sends the request to you and then breaks the connection. The connection does not resume again until you perform another function. To ensure that we maintain the connection between our server and your computer for the duration of an online transaction, we may use a standard web technology called "cookies." A "cookie" is a very small amount of data that is sent from our server to your computer's hard drive. "Cookies" allow us to save the information that you input while progressing through an online transaction. If your browser is not configured to accept "cookies," you still will be able to access the information on our website. No user information is gathered through "cookies" on our website.

##### Website Security

We maintain security standards and procedures regarding unauthorized access to ensure that the Mega Millions website remains available to all users and to prevent unauthorized attempts to upload or change information or otherwise cause damage to the site. Information on individuals causing, or attempting to cause, damage to the website will be traced and released to the appropriate legal authorities to investigate suspected or actual criminal activity.

##### Disclaimer

For your convenience the Mega Millions website may provide links to other sites. However, Mega Millions is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of the websites to which we link. When you link to another site you are no longer on the Mega Millions website, and this Privacy Statement will not apply. When you link to another website, you are subject to the privacy policy of that new site. If you have questions or concerns about a site to which we link, please read the privacy and security information for that site.

Mega Millions does not warrant the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of any information published on the Mega Millions website or any site to which we link, nor endorse any content, viewpoint, product or service linked from this system and shall not be liable for any loss caused by reliance on the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of such information. Portions of such information may be incorrect or not current. Any person or entity that relies on any information obtained from this system does so at his or her own risk.

##### Contact Information

To offer comments about the Mega Millions website or about the information presented in this Privacy Statement you may contact us by email at [webmaster@megamillions.com](mailto:webmaster@megamillions.com)
